大人物 某天脸上沾满泥 大耻辱 到处挥舞你的旗帜 看吧 我们会的 我们会的 起来，起来，起来，起来，起来
Big man someday got mud on your face Big disgrace waving your banner all over the place See it We will We will Get up, get up, get up, get up, get up
我们会的 但你是个老人 可怜的人 祈求安宁 某天 那脸上的泥 大耻辱 到处挥舞你的旗帜 看吧 我们会的 我们会的 今晚让你摇滚 我们会的，我们会的，我们会的摇滚
We will But you're an old man poor man Preetingiturize gonna get you some peace Someday That mud on your face Big disgrace Waving your banner all over the place See it We will We will rock you tonight We will, we will, we will rock
一 一 摇滚你。
One One Rock you.
今晚，我们会的，我们会的。
Tonight, we will, we will.
摇滚到摇滚，摇滚，摇滚，摇滚。
Rock to rock, rock, rock, rock.
我们会的，我们会的。
We will, we will.
我们会的。
We will.
开火！
Fire!
塞拉戈！
Serrago!
好久不见。
Long time, no see.
好吧，你想疯狂一把？
Okay, you want to get crazy?
来吧，咱们开始。
Come on, let's do it.
欢迎各位女士先生们。我想
Welcome you, ladies and gentlemen. I would like
向你们问好。准备好享受游泳
to say hello. Are you ready for swimming
娱乐了吗？准备好看一场表演了吗？
entertainment? Are you ready for a show? Gonna
我要让你们摇摆，让你们滚动，让你们的眼神
rock you, gonna roll you, get your dancing in the
充满舞动。爵士乐响起，我带着一点
eyes. Jazzy, runs and I'm dancing with a little
风格起舞。让我来娱乐你们。
bit of style. Let me entertain you. Let me
让我来娱乐你们。
entertain you.
来这里，我要向你们展示我的身体。我可以
Come here to sell you my body. I can show you
给你们看一些精彩的骰子游戏。
some good much of dice.
皮迪奥和我们的观点。我会创造你们。我会
Pidio and our opinion. I'll create you. I'll use
使用任何手段。
any device.
我们会给你们疯狂的表演。我们会给你们
We'll give you crazy performers. We'll give you
发声的理由。
grounds for your voice.
我们会给你们节日的抵抗者。
We'll give you Fiesta resistors.
而我，会带来分离。
And I'll do divorce.
从你们正确的位置，许多美丽的眼睛，
From your right location, a lot of pretty eyes,
通知的声音，听好了。
sound of notification, listen.
如果你需要一剂，如果你想隐藏，贴纸
If you need a fix, if you want to hide, stickers
会看到床，伴随着讲座和GMR，我们
will see the bed, with the lecture and GMR, we'll
会向你展示悲伤所在。
show you where it's sad.
让我来娱乐你们。
Let me entertain you.
是的，让我来娱乐你。
Yeah, let me entertain you.
让我来娱乐你。
Let me entertain you.
你。
you.
哦，让我来娱乐你。
Oh, let me entertain you.
好的。
All right.
就看看菜单吧。
Just take a look at the menu.
我们为你带来摇滚全车。
We give you rock all the car.
早餐，那是胆小鬼的。
The breakfast, that's timidies.
我们用日语向你保证安全。
We're safe to you in Japanese.
我们在这里只是为了娱乐你。
We're only here to entertain you.
你。哦，我看到一些动作。
You. Oh, I see some action.
除了那个人什么都没有。
Got nothing but the man.
是的，有那么大的吸引力，我们得把
Yes, and that much traction, we got to place the
箱子。从芝加哥到新最少，那是从线开始的。
chest. Chicago down to New Least, that's from the line.
如果你靠近，我见过，一些
If you take the near, I've seen, some of the
时间的海滩。
beach of the time.
让我娱乐，今晚让我娱乐你。
Let me entertain, let me entertain you tonight.
今晚让我理解你。
Let me understand you tonight.
我说，让我来娱乐你。
I said, let me entertain you.
谢谢。
Thank you.
让我走进来，放下你的意愿，让你的心决定。这很容易，当你知道规则时，这很容易。
Let me step inside Rest your will and let your heart decide It's so easy When you know the rules, it's so easy
你只需坠入爱河，玩这场游戏，每个人都参与其中。我的爱之名，是的，当你沉沦，当你的爱意抵抗不住，再点一支烟，让你停下脚步。这是你的人生，别玩难以捉摸的游戏，这是个艰难的游戏，却也是自由的世界。你只需坠入爱河，玩这场游戏，每个人都参与其中。哦，爱啊，是的，我的游戏结束了，却又刚刚开始。爱意从头顶涌至脚尖，我的爱在床榻间跳跃，驱策你自己，玩这场游戏，玩这场游戏，玩这场游戏，玩这场游戏。
All you have to do is fall in love Play the game Everybody play the game My name of love Yeah When you're When you're sealing down And your resistance in love Light another cigarette And let you stop go This is your life Don't play hard to game It's a hard to game It's a free wall All you have to do is fall in love Play the game Everybody play the game Oh love Yeah Yeah My game over That's just begun Love runs from my head up to my toes My love is bumping To my bed Driving me yourself Play the game Play the game Play the game Play the game.
每个人都参与这场游戏。
Everybody play the game.
哦，不。是的，这是你的人生。
Oh, no. Yes, this is your life.
别玩那难以捉摸的游戏。
Don't play how to game.
这是个自由，自由的世界。
It's a free, free world.
你只需坠入爱河。
All you have to do, fall in love.
玩这场游戏，每个人都参与其中。
Play the game, everybody play the game.
有人能签下我吗？
Can anybody sign me?
某人，某人。
Somebody, somebody.
某人。
Somebody.
有人，能找到某人吗？
Somebody, can somebody find?
嗯，某人，哦。
Uh, somebody, oh.
某人，某人爱着。
Somebody, somebody loves.
好吧，我们开始吧。
Okay, let's do it.
每个早晨，我唤醒我的孩子，
Each morning I get out my child,
悉心照料，却已厌倦了我的脚步。
care, and it's tired of my feet.
照照镜子，泪水滑落，
Take a look, take the mirror, and cry,
你对我做了什么？
what's you do to me?
我倾尽所有年华，与你共信共守。
I have spent all my years and believe with you.
却始终无法得到一丝慰藉。
I just can't get no relief on.
某人，某人，某人，某人。
Somebody, somebody, somebody, somebody.
任何人。
Anybody.
我需要有人来爱。
I need somebody to love.
我日复一日辛勤工作。
I work right every day of my life.
直到筋疲力尽，骨头酸痛。
I work till I ache my bones at the end.
在一天结束之时。
At the end of the day.
我倾注全部心血。
I take all my heart of me all.
我独自一人。
I'm on my own.
我跪地祈祷，直至泪水盈眶。
I'm on my knees and I start to pray till the tears are down from my eyes.
在我的眼中。
On my eyes.
某人。
Somebody.
每个人。
Everybody.
每个人都像我一样。
Everybody's like me.
有人爱。
Somebody love.
他辛勤工作。
He works hard.
他每天都在辛勤工作。
He works hard every day.
我尝试，再尝试，不断努力。
Try and I try and I try and try.
每个人都想把我打倒。
Everybody wants to put me down.
他们说我快要疯了。
They say I'm going to crazy.
这将渴望成为我的朋友。
This is going to want to want to be my friends.
我得交些朋友。
I've got to come friends.
但没人留下离开。
But nobody left to leave.
耶，耶，耶，耶，耶，耶。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
有人，有人，有人，任何人找到我，
Somebody, somebody, somebody, anybody find me,
某个低落的人。
somebody low.
耶！
Yeah!
感觉就像在河里，我不断失去
Got to feel like in the river, I just keep losing
我的节奏。
my beat.
我没事，我很好，我要战斗，阻止
I'm okay, I'm all right, I'm gonna fight, stop a
费用，我只想逃离，
fee, I just gotta get out,
这座监狱，总有一天我会获得自由，
of this prison said one day I'm gonna be freed,
主啊。就这样！
Lord. That's all!
耶，耶，耶，耶。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
好吧，耶，耶，耶。
All right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
做吧，宝贝。
Do it, baby.
继续下去。
Keep it going.
与我战斗，寻找某人去爱。
Fight me, somebody to love.
去爱，找到我去爱的人，找到我去爱的人，找到我去爱的人，找到我去爱的人，与我战斗，寻找某人去爱。
to love find me somebody to love find me somebody to love find me somebody to love find me somebody to love Fight me somebody to love.
寻找我。一个值得爱的人。
Find me. Somebody to love.
与我较量。一个值得爱的人。
Fight me. Somebody to love.
寻找我。一个值得爱的人。
Find me. Somebody to love.
某人。某人。
Somebody. Somebody.
某人。
Somebody.
寻找我。某人。
Find me. Somebody.
某人。
Somebody.
去爱。
To love.
任何人。
Anybody.
寻找我。
Find me.
某人爱。
Somebody love.
寻找我。
Find me.
爱。寻找我。
Love. Find me.
爱。一个值得爱的人。
Love. Somebody to love.
是的。某人。
Yeah. Somebody.
是的。去爱。
Yeah. To love.
去爱。
Do love.
真的。
Really.
某人。
Somebody.
去爱。
Do love.
哦。哦。哦。哦。哦。
Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh.
哦。你能找到我吗？
Oh. Can you find me?
你能找到我吗？
Can you find me?
是的。是的。哦，是的。
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
哦。是的。哦，我剩下的坚强。
Oh. Yeah. Oh, I rest of the strong.
哇达，巴达，瓦拉，是的，是的，是的。
Wada, barda, va la, yeah, yeah, yeah.
所以。
So.
听着，如果你们想动一动，稍微挪挪
Listen, if you guys want to move around and shift
你们的屁股，没关系的。
your asses a little, it's okay.
我们觉得没问题，对吧？
It's okay by us, right?
如果你愿意，也可以把所有的衣服都带走。
You can take all your clothes up if you like too.
怎么了？
What matter?
滚开。
Fuck off.
这叫做杀手皇后。
This is called Killer Queen.
她总是远离沙尔瓦姆。
She keeps from always Shalwa'am.
她把她的摩什放在一个漂亮的柜子里。
She keeps the moish of her in a pretty cabinet.
让它们成为蛋糕，她就像玛丽·安托瓦内特一样被抚养长大。
Let them be cake, she's raised, just like Marie
安托瓦内特。
Antoinette.
肯尼迪家族的游艇建筑与补救，以及你无法拒绝的邀请。
The building and remedy for cruise of a Kennedy and at an entitlement invitation you can't decline.
骑兵，香烟，每个罐子里都装得满满的。
Cavalions, cigarettes, well-bursed in every can't.
她是个杀手。
She's a killer.
我们拥有切尔曼尼的一部分，
We've got part of chelmany,
带有激光瞄准器的炸药。
dynamite with a laser bead.
丹尼特。
Danyte.
用来部署一个思想。
to deploy a mind.
随时。
Anytime.
推荐其他费用。
Recommended other costs.
这是为食欲而设的站点。
It's station for an appetite.
想试试。
Want to try.
是的，试试看。
Yeah, and try.
为了制造复杂情况，你从未保持同一个地址。
To provide complications, you never kept the same
对话中你说话就像个男爵夫人。
address.
你刚才的谈话就像一片荒芜。
Conversation you spoke just like a barreness.
她与中国男人的审讯，小事一桩。
Men of her with China and interrogation, minor.
那我在中国搞定它。
Then I'll get it in China.
那我就深入其中。
Then I'll get into it.
再次，用那种方式隐藏的事件。
Then again, incident with that way to hide.
从巴黎给阿什莉的完美游戏。
Perfew game to Ashley from Paris.
因为她毫不在意，那声望，那精确。
Because she could careless, the stigious, precise.
她是个杀手。
She's a killer.
我们得到了三位一体的一部分，
We got part of Trinity,
为激光束准备的炸药。
dynamite for the laser beam.
保证我的荣耀。
Guarantee to glory of mine.
而我是一个坚定的广告。
And I'm a committed advertisement.
是个男孩，我在尝试。
It's a boy and I'm a try.
想要尝试。
Want to try.
我将成为一台机器，一个梦，如此洁净的机器。
I'm going to be a Machine, a dream, such a clean machine.
活塞在泵动，钩子全部伸出，
The pistons are pumping, and the hook comes all
蓝色。
blue.
当我握住你的赢家，
When I'm holding your winner,
我只听到你的给予者，
all I hear is your giver,
你的手在我的润滑油枪上，
your hand on my grease gun,
就像一种病，我爱上了我的车。
It's like a disease, I'm in love with my car.
哦，不。它对我的汽车有了感觉。
Oh, no. It's got a feel for my automobile.
抓紧我的男孩，赛车，翻滚。
Get a grip by my boy, race, and roll.
当你收音机尖叫时，如此电影化。
Such a film when you're radio squeal.
这是你创作的轨迹，说道，现在就是终点。
This is you make track, said, this is the end now.
Cies不会回头。
Cies don't turn back.
他们现在只会磨损友谊。
They're just going to wear friends now.
谢谢。
Thanks.
我将成为。
I'm going to be.
我给你温暖。
I give you heat.
你说你饿了。
You say you hungry.
我给你肉。
I give you meat.
我吸取你的思想。
I suck your mind.
你让我头脑发热。
You blow my head.
制定一条法则。
Make a law.
在你的床上，所有人，趴下。
Inside your bed, everybody, get down.
制定一条低调的法则。
Make a low.
趴下，制定低调。
Get down, make a low.
起来。
Get up.
你说你想冷静下来。
You say you want to cool out.
说这很简单。
Say it's simple.
背后太过沉重。
The back is too much.
确实。我想趴下。
True. I want to get down.
趴下。
Get down.
Brian一会儿弹钢琴，等他准备好了。
Brian's gonna play piano in a minute when he gets to it.
这首歌来自一张名为《游戏》的专辑。
This is from an album called The Game.
让我们去拯救我。
Let's go save me.
起初一切美好 他说我们打造了完美的床 我沉浸在你的荣耀与爱中 我是多么爱你，多么哭泣
It started off so well He said we made a perfect bed I closed myself in your glory and love how I loved you, how I cried
多年的关怀与全心全意 似乎只是一场虚妄 他目盲，我们活着 我爱你至死不渝 救救我 救救我 我无法面对他的生活 主啊 救救我，救救我
Years of care and whole of two Nothing but a sham it seemed He is blind we live I love you till I die Save me Save me I can't face his life for Lord Save me, save me on
赤裸裸，我远离家园 奴隶渴望洁净 我不会唤起任何记忆 重新开始与新人共度 但你总说那爱 我低头，我宣扬 一个灵魂漂泊无依 我无心，我被召唤 我无真实意图 让我看清自己 救救我 救救我 救救我 海角天涯 我生来赴死 救救我，是的
naked and I'm far from home The slave will to be clean on I'll raise no memory To start again with somebody new but you would always tell all that love I hang my head and I advertise A soul to sail rent I have no heart I'm called inside I have no real intent Let me see me Save me Save me Save me Cape Faces I'm born to die Save me, yeah.
救救我
Save me.
哦，萨米
Oh, Sammy.
别让我独自面对人生
Don't let me face my life alone.
救救我，救救我
Save me, save me.
救救我
Save me.
哦，哦，哦，远离你，我挣扎求生
Oh, oh, oh, making it out of far from you.
哦。哦。哦。我站在这里
Oh. Oh. Oh. Here I stand.
环顾四周，四周，四周，四周，四周
Look around, around, around, around, around.
但你渴望见到你
But you want to see you.
现在我在这里
Now I'm here.
现在我到了那里
Now I'm there.
是的，你或许能重生
Yes, you may be live again.
无论你我之间发生了什么
Whatever came of you and me,
美国的新娘即将到来。
America's new bride to be.
我知道的宝贝，我会保存那些声音，
I know my babe, I'll save them sound
在沙滩与我的地牢深处。
down in the dungeons of beaches and me.
看起来像追逐。
Look like chase.
别动，别说话，别感到痛苦。
Don't move, don't speak, don't feel no pain.
当你在我脸上方，
When you're on top of my face,
你依然照亮天际，
that you still light up the sky,
直到它只属于我。
many until it's on my own.
在城市深处，我将会是谁？
Down in the city, just who will I be?
我愿将我的记忆留给你。
I'd love to leave my memory with you.
我说耶，耶，耶耶耶耶耶，
I say yeah, yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah yeah ,
好吧好吧好吧好吧好吧耶耶耶耶来吧，尘土到脚边耶耶耶耶
All right All right all right All right all right Yeah yeah Yeah yeah Come on dirt to the feet Yeah yeah Yeah, yeah
好了，好了好了好了，好了
Alright, all right Alright Alright, alright
好的，好的好的，好吧我发誓耶，耶。
Okay, okay Okay, all right I swear to yeah, yeah.
耶，耶，耶，是的，耶，耶。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yeah, yeah.
我说过的话。
what I said.
耶。来吧。带我去那个房间，那里的绿色如我所见般翠绿。
Yeah. Come. Take me to the room where the greens are green from what I see.
它很高。它是真实的。
It's high. It's the real.
节拍环绕之处，我将尽情享受，直至我离开。
Where the beats are around, I'll eat that I'm out.
是啊，是啊，是啊。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
没错。
Yeah.
带我去那个房间，当黑色全变白，
Take me to the room while the black's all white,
白色全变黑，带我回到
and the white's all black, took me back to the
天空。
sky.
不俘虏任何人，也不做那
Not to use no prisoners, not going to do the
交易。
business.
我的床上有一颗钻石。
Got a diamond on my bed.
而她正驾驶着她的椅子。
And she's driving her chair.
我想我会留下来，留下来，留下来。
I think I'm gonna stay around, around, around.
请留下 请留下 请留下 就在山谷里，只有你和我 只有你和我 一分钟 有很多 你有心情唱歌吗？
Please stay Please stay Please stay Down in the valley just to you and me Just to you and me One minute It's a lot of Are you in the mood for singing?
不。给我们一点帮助吧。
No. Give us a little help with this.
这是我生命中的爱。
This is love of my life.
你记得这个。
You remember this.
我生命中的爱，你已听闻 你伤透了我的心，现在你要离开 我生命中的爱，你看不见吗 带它回来，带它回来 别把它从我身边带走，因为 你不知道它对我意味着什么 我生命中的爱，别离开我。
Love of my life you've heard You've broken my heart and now you leave me Love of my life can't you see Bring it back bring it back Don't take it away from me because You don't know what it means to me Love of my life, don't leave me.
我偷走了我的爱，我渴望自己。
I'm stolen my love, and I'm desire me.
我生命中的爱，你看不见吗？
Love of my life, can't you see?
把它带回来，带回来，
Bring it back, bring it back,
别从我身边夺走，因为你不知道它对我意味着什么。
don't take it away from me because you don't know what it means to me.
当这一切过去，一切归于爱时，你会记得。
You will remember when this is blown over and everything's all by love.
当我年岁渐长，我会在你身旁，
When I grow older, I will be there at your side
提醒你我依然爱你，我依然爱着
to remind you how I still love you, I still love
你。
you.
去爱它。
To love it.
哦，快回来，快回来，别从我身边夺走，因为你不知道它对我意味着什么，我生命中的爱，我生命中的爱，压在我身上，压在你身上，无论
Oh hurry back Hurry back Don't take it away from me because you don't know what it means to me Love of my life Love of my life pressing down on me, pressing down on you, no
是谁的错。
matter's fault.
在压力之下，那燃烧着整栋建筑，它
Under pressure, that burns the building down, it's
是一个真正的家庭。
a family in truth.
那些人如糖果般甜美。
Those people are sweets.
一点点，尝一口，吃下去，吃下去。
A bit, pop of it, eat it up, eat it up.
那是对抗这世界即将到来的恐怖。
That's against the terror of knowing this world is about.
我追逐着一些好朋友，尖叫着，不，让
Well, I chase some good friends, scream, no, let
我出去。
me out.
祈祷明天，它会更高地亲吻我。
Pray tomorrow, it'll kiss me higher.
压力压在人们身上，如同棍棒。
Pressure on people on sticks.
哒，哒，哒，哒，哒。
Da, da, da, da, da.
哒，哒，哒。
Da, da, da.
四处漂泊，我的思绪散落一地。
Shipping around, my brain's on the floor.
他全是膝盖。
He's all the knees.
天不下雨，却总在召唤。
It never rains, but it calls.
街上的人们。迪塔，迪塔，达达，达达，达达。
People on streets. Dita, Dita, Dada, Dada, Dada.
迪塔。达达，达达。杜阿。
Dita. Dada, Dada. D'u'a.
德拉。
D'ra.
街上的人们。
People on streets.
达达，德拉，街上的人们。
Dada, de la, people on streets.
迪塔，哒哒，哒哒，哒。
Dita, de da, de da, da.
这是知晓世界真相的恐惧。
It's the terror of knowing what this world is about.
看着一些好朋友，梦想家，让我出去。
Watching some good friends, dreamer, let me out.
这是明天。
It's tomorrow.
是的，我怎样，呀，怎样。
Yes, me how, ya, how.
哦。我...
Oh. I...
转身离开它，空间。
Turn the way from it, space.
像盲人一样转身远离这一切。
Turn the way from it all like a blind man.
坐在篱笆上，但无济于事。
Sat on a fence, but it don't work.
不断陷入爱河，却如此破碎且
Keep coming up in love, but it's so slashed and
高耸。
tall.
为什么？
Why?
如果我们疯狂，压力下大笑，我们哭泣，能否再给自己一次机会？为何不能给予爱，再给一次机会，为何不能给予爱？
If we're Insanity laughs under pressure We're crying Can we give ourselves One more chance Why can we give love And one more chance Why can we give love?
给予爱，给予爱，给予爱
Give love give love, give love
Give love, give love, give love
因为爱是如此古老的字眼，而爱让你关心夜晚边缘的人们，爱让你改变我们关心自己的方式，这是我们的最后一舞，这是我们的最后一舞。
Because love such an old-fashioned world And loved as you to care for the people on the edge of the night And love there's you to change our way of caring about ourselves This is our last dance This is our last dance.
这是我们自己，在压力之下，在压力之下，我要释放它！
This is ourselves Under pressure Under pressure I'm Shag it out!
释放它！
Shack it up!
嗯哼！
Uh-huh!
我曾被所有困扰我的问题短暂出卖，为了每天成长得更明智、更好一点，但即使我跨越百万河流，骑行百万英里，史努比，我仍始于何处，孕育并作为父亲为...
I was sold in a little time of all the troubles in my way To grow a little whyser a little better every day But if I crossed a million rivers and I rode a million miles Snoopy where I started, bred and father for a
微笑 在购物小巷里卖出了百万女孩的心 但我从未在任何橱窗中见过自己的面容 如今你说你的书让你烦透了 成为超级巨星吧 心满意足地 留在原地 让自己活下去 在你的次生命中 你所爱的一切只为生存 我是Belletoddy之吻，拥有亿万星辰的追随 给我所需的一切，滋养我的身体与灵魂 再滚大一点，宝贝们回到光束中
smile Sold a million of girls with a shopping alleyway But I never saw my face in any window any day Now you say your books are fucking you Be a superstar Deliciously satisfied Stay where you are Keep yourself alive In your sub-life All you be love to survive I'm Belletoddy kiss and I had a billion to the stars to me on to trace Give me everything I need feed my body and my soul Roll a little bigger, babies back to the beam I
前行 为了那无数次挡在我路上的所有人 我必须不断尝试，每天变得更好 即便我要横渡百万条河流，
go For all the million times of all the people were in my way I had to keep on trying and get better every day And if I cross to the million rivers,
划行百万英里 只为填满我出发的地方，
A row and a million miles To fill me where I started,
如同我初启程时一样 让自己活下去，让自己活下去
Same as when I started Keep yourself alive, keep yourself alive
所有人啊，保持自我一致。
All you people, keep your self-aligned.
水。
Shui.
美利坚 它整夜像摇篮里的婴儿般哭泣 它摇摆不定 它四处囚禁，如水母般 有点疯狂的小家伙 我的宝贝就这样离去 她不懂摇滚与摇滚乐 她让我疯狂 她给我炽热而紧密的激情 她在清凉的汗水中击败我 必须保持冷静 好吧，我会保持冷静
The United States It cries like a baby in a cradle all night It swings over It jails all over like the jellyfish Kind of like it Crazy little man That goes my baby She knows not rock and rock and roll She drives me crazy She gives me hard and close fever She beats me in a cool cool sweat sweat Gotta be cool Well, I'm gonna be cool
好吧，我说
Well, I said
过来 登上我的垃圾车 坐到后座 每次高潮 在我的边界上长途骑行 直到我准备好 疯狂的爱无处不在
Get here Get on my trash To take the back seat Each high Take a long ride on my border Back until I'm ready Crazy love in all over.
铁轨斧，被击中，踏上我的轨道，紧贴
Rail-axe, get hit, get on my tracks, stick the
后座，搭便车，
back seat, hitchhike,
在我的摩托车上长途骑行，直到我准备好，
take a long ride on my motorbike until I'm ready,
准备好，
ready,
去培育一颗小大的橄榄，这么大，疾驰，我
to raise a little big olive, this big, gallop, I
知道。
know.
举起你的小东西，哦，
Raise your little thing on, oh,
举起你的小大，哦，
Raise your little big, oh,
举起你的小点，哦，举起你的小蛋，
Raise your little bit, oh, raise your little egg,
哦，来吧，
oh, come,
哦，举起你的小东西，拿它，拿它，
Oh, raise your little thing on, take it, take it,
拿它。
take it.
养一只小黄鸟。
Raise a little yellow.
在县监狱里。
in the county jail.
有一支乐队，我们以此开始。
There's a band that we began with.
乐队开放，再次跳跃，我们摇摆。
The band was open and the jump again we swing.
又在监狱度过紧张的一夜，但你看到了
Shoot a other night tight jail, but you see the
最后的旅程。
last ride.
今晚每个人都摇滚起来。
Everybody rock and roll tonight.
来吧。霍特肖博客里的每个人。
Come. Everybody in the Hotschow blog.
随着死亡冰之旅起舞。
Dance to the Dead Ice ride.
现在站在你的位置上，设定第三号。
Now upon your stand and set up number three.
年轻的美女说，但我从未见过。
Young cutie tell, but I ever did see.
在你的陪伴中展现我的喜悦。
Show me being delighted in your company.
我要做死亡之眼摇滚和我。
I'm going to do the Dead Eyes Rock and Me.
让我们摇滚吧。
Let's rock.
每个人都摇滚并咆哮着前行。
Everybody rock and roared to ride.
马背上的每个人都在摇滚。
Everybody in the horse and rock.
随着卡车的尾部起舞。
Dance to the tail of the truck.
来吧。
Come on.
谢谢。
Thank you.
她随着裁缝的墙起舞，随着歌曲的尾部起舞，来吧，做吧。
She danced to the tailors' wall Dance to the tail of the song Do it, come on.
跳舞，随着歌曲的尾部起舞
Dancing, dance to the tail of song
还有你们这些家伙，来吧，耶，耶，耶，耶，
And your fuckers, come on, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
是啊，是啊，是啊，
yeah, yeah, yeah,
好吧，跳舞，跳舞，跳舞，
all right, dancing, dancing, dancing,
跳到尾吧，
dance to the tailout bar,
跳到聊天，离球，跳到聊天，
dance to the chat, off ball, dance to the chat,
妈妈，就杀了那个人，用枪抵住他的
Mama, just kill the man, put a gun against his
头，扣动扳机，美好的一天。
end, pulled my trigger nice day.
妈妈，生活才刚刚开始。
Mama, life had just begun.
但我必须把它全部抛掉。
But I've got to throw it all the way.
妈妈，哦，本不想让你哭泣
Mama, ooh, didn't need to make you cry
如果这次我明天不再回来。
if I'm not back again this time tomorrow.
继续，继续。
Carry on, carry on.
一切都不重要了。
Nothing really matters.
太迟了，我的时间已逝。
Too late, my time has gone.
自从脊背发凉，但他一直痛苦
Since shivers down my spine, but he's aching all
不已。
the time.
再见，各位。
Goodbye, everybody.
我得走了。
I've got to go.
但我把你们都留在了身后。
But I leave you all behind.
心已坠落。
the heart I fell.
真的。妈妈，哦。
True. Mom, oh.
哦，哦。
Oh, oh.
我不想死。
I don't want to die.
我停止了最艰难的愿望，希望从未离家。
I stopped the toughest wish I'd never been by home.
一个男人的小丑，斯卡拉穆什，斯卡拉穆什，你
Aluetto of a man Scaramouche, scaramouche, will
会跳班丹戈舞吗？
you do the bandango?
丑闻如闪电，非常，非常
Scandal-a-Mobile lightning, very, very
让我害怕。
frightening me.
伽利略，伽利略，接听班西菲科的电话！
Galileo, Galileo, pick up on Bancifico!
我只是个可怜的孩子，没人爱我。
I'm just a poor boy and nobody loves me.
他只是个来自四大家族的可怜孩子，从这场轻松的十字架中
He's just a poor boy from the four family, sparing
救了他的命。
his life from this one's cross-a-easy.
来得容易，去得也快，你会让我走吗？
Easy come, easy go, will you let me go?
比斯米拉。
Bishmila.
不，我们不会让你走。
No, we will not let you go.
让他走。
Let him go.
比斯米拉。
Bismillah.
你们不会让你走。
You will not let you go.
让他走。
Let him go.
让我走。
Let me go.
你们不会让你走。
You will not let you go.
永远不让我走。
Never let me go.
不，永远不让我走。
No, never let me go.
哦，不，啦，不，不，不，不。哦，妈妈我，妈妈，妈妈，我。
Oh, no, la, no, no, no, no. Oh, mamma me, mama, mama, me.
妈妈咪呀，让我走。
Mama Mia, let me go.
菲亚尔兹和投票，有个魔鬼为我留了一手。
Fialz and vote has a devil put aside for me.
哦，我。
Oh me.
哦，我。总统我将成为，任何人都看不见。
Oh, me. The President I'm going to be the Anyone can't see.
其实没什么大不了的。
Nothing really matters.
对我来说，其实没什么大不了的。
Nothing really matters to me.
无论风往哪里吹。
Anywhere the wind blows.
我从未从你和你的家族中得到任何尊重，事实上，我从未听过一句客气话。你们这些人，现在我不会再是那个生活的主角，我要纠正一切，让一切变得更甜蜜些。阻止你们所有人，叫嚣着，而我正奋力抗争。把你母亲绑起来，把你母亲绑起来，带着你的小弟弟去游泳，手里拿着砖头，没关系，把你母亲绑起来。是的，她不是我的朋友，她不是我的朋友。我希望能成为某个大人物。
sold I ever get from you And your family ties In fact I never heard A civil little world You guys Now I don't be the life Gonna make a right A little sweeter hair Stop you all there Shouting and I'm fighting good on Tie your mother down Tie your mother down Take your little brother Swimming with a brick That's all right Tie your mother down Yeah She ain't a friend of mine She ain't a friend of mine I'm like to be so big some guy.
把它给我。
Give it to me.
我想要它。
I want it.
是的，今晚你所有的爱。
Yeah. All your love tonight.
我想要它。
I want it.
让我今天得到你的爱。
Let me get you on your love today.
你所有的爱。
All your love.
今天你所有的爱。
All your love today.
射击吧。
Shoot out.
史蒂夫走在街上，没注意到自己脚步声，机关枪镀金闪耀，你准备好了吗？
Steve walks down the street Ain't know the sound of his feet Machine guns railed gold Are you ready?
嘿，你准备好迎接这个了吗？
Hey, are you ready to this?
你是否正坐在座位边缘，门外子弹、橡胶，随着节拍声响起。
Are you standing on the edge of seats Out the doorway the bullets, rubber, to the sound
的节奏。
of the beat.
嘿，耶，耶，耶。
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
看！
See!
又一个倒下了！
Another one bites the dust!
看外面！
See out!
看它！
See it!
又一个倒下了！
Another one bites a dust!
又一个走了，又一个来了，
And another one go, and another one comes,
又一个倒下了嘿，要抓住你们两个，又一个倒下了
Another one bites a dust Hey, gonna get you two, another one bites a dashed
枪战，哈！
Shootout, huh!
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，来吧。
Hey, hey, hey, hey, come on.
你觉得怎么样，会得到很多吗？
How do you think, gonna get a lot?
那就是你离开时的样子，
That's you when you're gone,
它夺走了我的一切，
it took me for everything that I had,
并在我一生中不断打击我。
and kicked me all of my life.
把我赶出了自己的世界。
kicked me out of my own.
你开心吗？
Are you happy?
我很满意。
I'm satisfied.
我能忍受这热度很久。
I long can stand the heat.
走出门口，耸耸肩，走向节奏旁边的河流。
Out the doorway to pull it shrug to the river at the side of the beat.
嘿，耶，耶，耶。
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
看，又一个倒下了。
See, another one bites a dust.
来吧，做吧。
Come on, do it.
又一个倒下了。
Another one bites a dust.
又一个走了，又一个走了，
And another one gone and another one gone,
又一个倒下了。
and another one bites of dust.
嘿，也要抓住你。
Hey, gonna get you too.
又一个倒下了。
Another one bites of dust.
射击它。
Shoot it.
射击它，戏弄它，戏弄它。
shoot it Trick it, trick it.
我是尘埃，我是另一个，宝贝，哦耶。
I'm the dust, I'm nother, baby, oh yeah.
又一个恶习将她化为尘埃。
Another one vice to dust her.
又一个家伙将她化为尘埃。
Another one guy's to dust her.
又一个最佳选择将她化为尘埃。
Another one best to dust her.
又一个恶习化为尘埃。
Another one vice to dust.
嘿，耶。
Hey, yeah.
它为你准备好了。
It's ready for you.
我站在我的手臂上。
I'm standing on my arm.
走出门外，村庄的河流伴随着我的声音。
Out the door where the village river to the sound of me.
嘿，嘿，耶，耶，耶。
Hey, hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
说，又一个倒下了，耶。
Say, another one bites a dust, yeah.
笨蛋，又一个倒下了。
Chump, another one bites a dust.
又一个消失了，又一个消失了，
And another one gone, and another one gone,
又一个化为尘埃。
another one bite to dust.
嘿，要抓住你们两个，又一个倒下了。
Hey, gonna get you two, another one bites a dust.
枪战。
Shootout.
耶。来吧，伙计。
Yeah. Come on, man.
来吧，伙计。
Come on, man.
耶，耶。
Yeah, yeah.
耶。哦，好吧。
Yeah. Oh, alright.
哦，对了。
Oh, right.
对了。
Right.
谢谢。
Thank you.
我将成为，而你才17岁。
I'm going to be the Well, you're just 17.
你只想消失不见。
All you want to do is disappear.
不想存在。
Don't want to be.
与我重复使用的话语繁多。
There's a lot of speech with me my reuse.
等等，你在试图成为的，我不在其中。
Wait, that you're trying to be, that I'm not in.
嘿，嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey, hey.
但团队就在那里。
But the team are there.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
是什么让我变成这样？
What made me this way?
你知道吗，亲爱的，不，亲爱的，我的感受如何。
Do you know, dear, no, dear, just how I feel.
不，亲爱的，不，亲爱的，不，只是不怪异。
Be no, dear, no, dear, no, just not weir.
看，耶。
See, yeah.
我感觉如此高涨，高涨，高涨。
I feel so in a higher, higher, higher.
打开电视，它正好映入我的眼帘。
turn on a TV that it turned out right in my eyes.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
灯光照在你脸上，大大的耻辱，踢你的
Light on your face, big disgrace, kicking your
猫满屋子跑，抓住你的。
cat all over the place, hold yours.
啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-
Be-E-E-E-E-R-E-R-Bull-P-Rour!
是的，继续唱吧。
Yeah, sing on.
看，外面！
See, out!
啤酒公牛，BORC！
Be-E-E-E-E-E-E-R-Bull, BORC!
耶！
Yeah!
巴里奥里-欧-欧-鲁尔，在街上大声呼喊，
Bally'Ory-E-E-Rull, shouting in the street,
总有一天要面对那堵墙。
gotta take on the wall someday.
脸上沾满鲜血，
Blood on your face,
大大的耻辱，宝贝，上下起伏无处不在，
big disgrace baby the up-down are all over the place,
接受它吧！
Take it!
啤-啤-啤-啤-啤酒-啤-带-来！
Be-E-E-E-E-R-B-R-Bring!
对，唱起来！
Yeah, sing on!
啤-啤-啤-啤-啤-妈！
Be-E-E-E-B-Maw!
没错。
Yeah.
老兄是个老人，穷人，可怜的家伙，
Buddy are an old man, poor man, pit-be-bitch,
总有一天这会让你挨揍，
That's gonna get you some beat someday,
脸上有污点，是耻辱，
matter on your face, be disgrace,
最好有人把你放回这里。
somebody better put you back in here.
拜托了。
Please.
嘿，为了你，来吧。
Hey, for you, Come on.
我们，我们要摇滚，唱出来。
We are, We're gonna rock, sing it.
我们会，我们会。
We will, we will.
对，再来一次，我们要，我们要。
Yeah, one more We're gonna We're gonna.
是的。我一次次付出代价，服完刑期，却未犯下罪行，也犯过一些大错，我承受过打击，也奉献过自己，但我依然怀揣希望。我们是冠军，我的朋友。
Yeah. I paid my dues Time after time I've done my sentence But committed no crime And bad mistakes I've made a few I've had my shells and gifted my breast But I've got blue We are the champions, my friend.
我们将狂欢至最后一刻。
And we'll give our party to the end.
我们是冠军。
We are the champions.
没有时间给失败者。
No time for losers.
我们是世界冠军。
We are the champions of the world.
我鞠躬致意。
I'm taking my bow.
我鞠躬致意，却无法呼唤。
I'm taking my bow and I couldn't call.
你带给我名望与财富，一切随之而来。
You brought me fame and fortune and everything goes.
我感谢你们所有人！
I thank you all!
但未曾有更美的玫瑰。
But it's been no better rose.
没有快乐能证明。
No pleasure proves.
我在考虑在百衣之前触碰。
I'm considering a touch before the hundred-a-dress.
我输了。
I lose.
继续，继续，继续。
On, on, on.
我们是冠军，我的朋友。
We are the champions, my friend.
我们将继续战斗。
And we'll be back fighting.
直到最后。
to the end.
哦，我们是冠军。
Oh, we are the champions.
我们是冠军。
We are the champions.
没有时间让我们失败。
No time for lose us.
我们是冠军。
We are the champions.
我们是冠军，我的朋友。
We are the champions, my friend.
我们将为战斗到底。
And we'll give our fighter to the end.
哦，我们是冠军。
Oh, we are the champions.
我们是冠军。
We are the champions.
没有时间给失败者，因为我们是冠军。
No time the loser, but we are champions.
那么，再见，Muncho。
So, goodbye, Muncho.
感谢你如此出色的表现。
Thank you for being such a good sport.